http://pelawgrange.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Who we are
Our website address is: http://pelawgrange.co.uk.
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Media
If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.
Contact forms
Cookies
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics
Who we share your data with
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
Your contact information
Additional information
How we protect your data
What data breach procedures we have in place
What third parties we receive data from
What automated decision making and/or profiling we do with user data
Industry regulatory disclosure requirements
Racing Office Opening Times
Monday
9.00am – 3.00pm
Tuesday
9.00am – 3.00pm
Wednesday
9.00am – 3.00pm
7.30pm Start
(Trials start at 6.30pm)
Sunday
6.11pm Start
(Trials start at 5.00pm)
Pelaw Grange Greyhound Shop
Purchase all your greyhound goods
Shop Now
About Us
Pelaw Grange Greyhound Stadium is a family owned business, racing under GBGB (Greyhound Board of Great Britain) rules and is situated in Pelaw Grange, Chester Le Street in the North East of England. It has been in the McKenna family since January 1965 and is now managed by Jeff McKenna.
Quick Links
Racing
Food & Drink
Retired Greyhounds
Contact Us
Contact Us
Pelaw Grange Greyhound Stadium
Drum Road, Chester-le-Street, Co. Durham, DH3 2AF.
Phone : (0191) 4102141
Fax : (0191) 4102235
Email : info@pelawgrange.co.uk
Copyright © 2016. All rights reserved. Design by Layer23
About Us
Terms & Conditions
Cookie Policy
Privacy Policy
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site we will assume that you are happy with it.Ok
